Chatlekha Klamruang

https://www.linkedin.com/in/chatlekha-klamruang chatlekhak@gmail.com | Edinburgh | +44-792-388-5056



EDUCATION

MSC.RENEWABLE ENERGY

EDINBURGH NAPIER UNIVERSITY, 2019 Dissertation: Feasibility study of integrating hybrid renewable energy microgrids in isolated island

BE.MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

KING MONGKUT UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY NORTH BANGKOK, 2011 Dissertation: Develop ROV prototype for underwater rescue

CERTIFICATION

- Analysing data with Python | 2020
- Data Analyst with SQL | 2020

LEADERSHIP

UK ARMY

Edinburgh, UK | February 2019 Team winner of Exercise Deep Heat -Leadership training

EDINBURGH NAPIER UNIVERSITY

Edinburgh. UK | September 2018 Student representative for MSc. Renewable Energy

TECHNIP ENGINEERING

Bangkok, Thailand | January 2014

- CSR leader: Successfully raised THB 100,000 for charity project
- HSE Representative: Conducted safety campaign in the department

KFY SKILLS

- AWS SQL Python Networking
- Project Management
 Data Analyst
- Network Security Database

SUMMARY

AWS re/Start program learner –working towards AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner. Experienced in using MATLAB, VBA, SQL for data analysis, as well as seven years of experience in the engineering field, focusing on energy industry and project management.

AWS RE/START

PRIMED TALENT LTD. I AWS CLOUD PRACTITIONER

February 2021 - Present | United Kingdom

- 12-week, full-time, classroom based skills development and training on IT fundamentals, AWS cloud and profession skills
- Applied core AWS services in the area of compute, storage and networking, including EC2, S3, IAM, VPC, Lamda, Cloud Formation, RDS and Route 53, IAM, VPC, Lambda, Cloud Formation, RDS, DynamoDB, Route53 in live environment
- Built IT fundamental skills including: working knowledge of Linux OS, writing scripts in Python and Shell, networking, security and relational database skills
- Learnt the principles of effective front-line support, troubleshooting, escalation, and task automation

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

SYSTEM LOGISTICS ASIA CO..LTD | PROJECT ENGINEER AND DATA ANALYST October 2015 - July 2018 | Bangkok, Thailand

- Worked in conjunction with Business Development Team to deliver suitable intralogistics solutions for clients, including analysed warehouse data with SQL and excel and project cost estimation.
- Monitored multiple projects and coordinated with colleagues in Italy and vendors to deliver the project on time.
- Attended marketing campaign to identify new project opportunities, successfully attracted new 50 projects over 3 years.

PT.TECHNIP INDONESIA | MECHANICAL ENGINEER

January - May 2015 | Jakarta, Indonesia

• On assignment to work in collaboration with Indonesian team in EPC project for ENI Jangkrik to perform Technical Bid Evaluation and clarification for Electric Heaters, Filters and Rectangular Tank. Effectively selected vendors based on client specification and international standards.

TECHNIP ENGINEERING (THAILAND) LTD. | MECHANICAL ENGINEER

May 2011 - July 2015 | Bangkok, Thailand

- Mechanical design and stress analysis by PV-elite for static equipment and packages for offshore platform, petrochemical plants according to ASME standards and client specifications.
- Accomplished, 2 EPC, 4 detailed engineering and 4 basic engineering projects for world leading oil and gas companies.
- Reviewed inter-discipline drawing and documents, PIDs, equipment layout, etc. Also liaised with clients to complete requisition review / approval and technical clarification.